* For Families
    
    * For Business

HT Vector Privacy Policy
========================

Your privacy is vital to HT Vector Inc. HT Vector Inc is committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors. This privacy policy discloses how we collect, protect, and use information you provide us online.

### Cookies

HT Vector gathers cookies like most websites. Cookies are automatically-collected data that does not link to personally identifiable information. When you visit our website, we may collect information regarding the type of browser you are using (Firefox, Google Chrome, etc.), the type of operating system you are using (Windows, Mac OS, etc.) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink, etc.). This non-personally identifiable information is used to make our website as usable as possible for the widest range of users. We use a third-party tracking service, Google Analytics, that uses cookies to track aggregate non-personally identifiable information about our site visitors.

### Information We Collect

When you purchase or register our products, or communicate with us by email or phone, we may collect identifiable information. We do not collect information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. We collect:

* Purchasing information such as your name, phone number, address, email address, payment history (date and amount).
* Registration information such as your license key, the email address connected with your purchasing, email address connected with your account, email address used for email reports, the computer name you installed our software, date of installation.
* Support information such as emails you send to our support or sales teams.

There is no other data held about our customers. Individual data is not processed, analyzed, mined, or profiled by anyone.

### We Do Not Collect

* We do not hold credit card information.
* We do not have access to information recorded or stored in our software.
* We do not have access to your account and information stored on it.
* We do not hold emailed reports. They are only transferred via our email server and are not saved on it.
* We do not know your access password for our software.

### HT Family Shield Online Dashboard

For HT Family Shield, we use a third-party highly protected store service, Google Firebase, that holds your settings and reports. We do not have access to your account and information stored on it. We can only delete your account from the server. Google Firebase ensures that this data will be secure. You will be the only person who has access to the data recorded or transmitted by our software.

### How We Use the Information

HT Vector does not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from that are described in this statement. We may use the personal and non-personal information collected to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your emails or inform you of our offers. We may also use it to understand your needs better, improve our website, software, and service.

### Purchase

Your purchase will be processed through [PayPro Global](https://payproglobal.com/about-us), one of the most trusted payment services in the world. Your data provided to Paypro Global is collected and stored on their secure server (SSL - Secure Socket Layers), using a firewall and a digital certificate issued by VerisignTM. Such secure servers make virtually impossible any attempt by third parties to access and/or use your data. Paypro Global provides us only your name, email, address, and phone number. HT Vector may use this information only in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy. We do not receive any information about your credit card or other payment details.

### Sharing of Information

HT Vector does not sell, share, or rent any data about you except where it is required by law or to protect and defend the rights or property of HT Vector. HT Vector may hire other companies such as Paypro Global and Google Firebase. These companies may have access to data as required to permit them to perform their obligations to us in this regard. All data is highly secured.

### Changes in Privacy Policy

We may occasionally update this privacy policy to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. If our privacy policy is changed, we will post those changes the policy changes on our website. Therefore our users can be always aware of what information we collect and how we use it. In any case, we will use information according to the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

### Privacy Questions

If you have questions or concerns about HT Vector’s Privacy Policy, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://ht-vector.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

_Last updated: March 14, 2020_

© 2007–2024  
All rights reserved

### Products

##### For Families

##### For Business

### Support

### Company

### Solutions
